<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Idang</string>
    <string name="crash_toast_text">Facing some issues</string>
  <string name="category_title"> Cairo the SEAL Dog</string>
    <string name="category_short_description">Cairo the military dog was born and bred for the job. He is a Belgian Malinois, a shepherd breed that few were familiar with, until Cairo’s story became news. After Cairo trained to be a Military Working Dog at a young age, he advanced to Navy SEAL training.</string>
    <string name="story_sample">Our nation\'s newest four-pawed super-hero is a dog named Cairo. \
And how much is a dog like him worth?
This is a case of;  “If you have to ask- you can’t afford him”, nor would this Top Dog ever be for sale.
Cairo is the hero-dog that accompanied SEAL Team 6 on their raid into the compound of Osama bin Laden in Abbottabad, Pakistan.
Cairo was born and bred to be a Military Working Dog. That in itself puts his price tag at over $20,000.
His puppyhood was spent in training to be a working dog. Following that, he was additionally trained to be a Navy SEAL-working dog.
Like all super-heroes Cairo has a “cape”. In this case, the “cape” is technically customized body armor and it costs upwards of $30,000.
Cairo’s specialized working gear is designed to make him bulletproof and while it doesn’t make him able to leap tall buildings in a single bound, it does enable him to hear through concrete and record missions in high-definition, even on the darkest nights.
Last year the U.S. military paid over $85,000 to K9 Storm, a contractor in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, for four tactical canine vests for the Navy\'s SEAL-dogs. K9 Storm has been gearing up war dogs since World War I.
K9 Storm’s premier product is the Intruder. Intruder is tactical body armor for dogs, with a selling price of $20,000 to $30,000 apiece, depending on the version. It comes wired with a collapsible video arm, two way-audio and other super-secret gadgets that civilians can only speculate about.
What is known, is that with the camera mounted on the dog’s back, his handlers, using handheld devices, see what the dogs sees.
The canine tactical assault vests for these wonder dogs weighs in at just three to five pounds.
Since, communication is key for the relationship with the K9 and his warrior, these “dogs of war” are trained one-on-one; one dog, one warrior and the bond with the two is closer than that of Batman and Robin.
It is well documented throughout the course of history that man\'s best friend is a fearsome warrior and loyal companion. Dogs have sacrificed their lives to save their soldier and no doubt more than one warfighter has given his life to save his dog.
SEAL-dogs are trained to work on land, in the air, and according to reports, underwater. Their doggie-armor is waterproof.
Navy SEALS aren’t the only Special Forces teams to use the specialized body armor for their K9 partners. Similar gear is used for military working dogs around the world.
So what is the value of a super-hero SEAL-dog? The answer, of course, is priceless.</string>
</resources>